Ruojin.
Then why did you hurt Xu Ruojin?
She has nothing to do with any of this.
Xu Ruojin didn't die, did she?
How much did the Wangs pay you?
For you to sell your soul to them.
I never cared about the money.
Then what is it?
Because of you.
Three-Seed Decoction clears damp-heat.
It needs Apricot Kernel,
Coix Seed,
Cardamom, Talc, Pinellia,
Tetrapanax Pith...
Feifan, you tell me.
I don't know either.
I really don't.
And Bamboo Leaf and Magnolia Bark.
You knew. Why didn't you say so?
I don't need you to go easy on me.
I've had nothing since I was a child.
I treated Master and Master's wife as family.
But they...
Putting on airs.
Fake kindness, phony virtue.
They only had eyes for you.
What do you have?
You just happen to share their blood.
Why must I live forever in your shadow?
That prescription...
we came up with it together.
But everyone gave you all the credit.
How is that fair?
Why?
Hurry up and search!
Yes, sir.
Move.
I want everyone to know
that they were all wrong.
All wrong.
And for that, you killed my whole family?
Junior Brother, when it comes down to it,
you should actually thank me.
Dad.
You're still alive.
As you can see,
I'm doing quite well.
Where is he?
In a very beautiful place.
Where?
Come on, Junior Brother.
Someone like you?
You can't save him.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Where?
He's...
in Wang Wenhao's hands.
Wang Wenhao.
You got three herbs wrong in Formula 37 of Treatise on Febrile Diseases.
Keep squatting.
You mixed up Angelica with Atractylodes.
Atractylodes.
You wrote Arisaema instead of Pinellia.
Arisaema.
Not one herb in a prescription can be wrong.
A miss is as good as a mile.
One wrong herb costs a life.
Do you understand?
Yes, Dad. I won't make that mistake again.
Keep squatting.
Brother.
If you make that prescription,
can it really save Dad from Wang Wenhao?
All of this...
Dazhuang's death...
Did Brother Hui really do it?
Forget about him.
Are Dazhuang's funeral arrangements settled?
This was his most precious possession.
He's already written so much.
He definitely would have been
a great doctor.
Master.
What's this?
Six qian.
Angelica.
Why Angelica?
Angelica and Earthworm can't be combined.
Change it.
Six qian of Goji Berry.
Alright.
Remember this well.
A miss is as good as a mile.
One wrong herb...
...costs a life.
Understood, Master.
I'll make sure to remember.
Thank you, Master.
You mixed up Angelica with Atractylodes.
Atractylodes.
You wrote Arisaema instead of Pinellia.
Arisaema.
Not one herb in a prescription can be wrong.
A miss is as good as a mile.
Brother.
What kind of prescription is this?
One that saves lives.
Wu Hui.
We're from the North City Police Department.
You're under arrest.
Here's the warrant.
Well played, Doctor Ren.
Playing pretty rough.
Sending your childhood friend to prison.
Speak.
What do you want from me?
Let's make a deal.
What kind of deal?
I have what you need.
Ren Feifan.
This new formulation of yours is terrifying.
Are you trying to kill me?
Extraordinary medicine yields extraordinary results.
The formulation of a prescription
requires both boldness and precision.
The previous dosage
you tested for four years
and never succeeded.
You've got nothing to lose by trying this.
Formulation is a craft.
Only experienced pharmacists
know how to blend these herbs.
Why should I trust you?
My father is in your hands.
I won't gamble with his life.
Fine.
I'll trust you for now.
When can I see him?
Master Ren, your food is here.
Okay.
Pebble.
Yeah?
You've taken care of me for so long,
but I never asked what your parents do.
I've been an orphan since I was little.
Villagers say I sprang out from a crack in a rock,
so they call me Pebble.
Master Ren,
you're a good person.
They're all bad people.
You're a clever kid.
Why don't you run away?